<News>
  <Article date="15 Feb 2018">
    <Title>
      New Gen 3 Pokemon and Enhanced <a href="charts/movesets/">Move Sets</a> pages.
    </Title>
    <Text>
      The various pages have been updated to show the new Gen 3 Pokemon that were released on 9 Feb 2018.
      <br /><span class="NOTE">(Sorry for the delay.)</span>
      <br />
      <br /><b style="margin-left:25px;">ALSO...</b>
      <br />
      <div class="PARENT">The Move Sets pages have had significant enhancements:</div>
      <ul class="CHILD">
        <li>Icons have been added to help you quickly see types and boosts.</li>
        <li>The ability to apply filters to narrow down what you are interested in.</li>
        <li>
          There is even an <a href="charts/movesets/movesets.all.html">All Generations</a> page. <span class="NOTE">(If you don't mind the extra loading time.)</span>
        </li>
      </ul>
      Take a look!
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="9 Feb 2018">
    <Title>
      New <a href="tools/shoppingboxes.html">Shopping Boxes!</a>
    </Title>
    <Text>
      With the release of new Gen 3 Pokemon, there are new Shopping Boxes.
      <br />Check out how much they are worth <b>
        <i>to YOU</i>
      </b>!
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="8 Feb 2018">
    <Title>
      More Enhancements to <a href="/charts/pokechart.html">
        Pokemon Chart <span class="NOTE TODO"> (Beta)</span>
      </a>
      <br /> - AND -
      <br /><a href="/charts/raidboss/raidboss.rayquaza.html">Rayquaza</a> Becomes Tier 5 RaidBoss!
    </Title>
    <Text>
      I have added more details in the Pokemon Chart <span class="NOTE TODO"> (Beta)</span> in the Charts section.
      <br />And it has been announced that Rayquaze will become a RaidBoss starting 9 Feb 2018, so I have moved it to the Tier 5 Raid Bosses.
      <br />
      <br /><b>
        <i>Also:</i>
      </b>
      <br />It has been announced that more Gen 3 Pokemon will be released 9 Feb 2018, along with new Raid Bosses.
      As soon as I have the list, I will update the various pages.
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="26 Jan 2018">
    <Title>
      New <a href="/charts/pokechart.html">
        Pokemon Chart <span class="NOTE TODO"> (Beta)</span>
      </a>  In The Charts Section!
    </Title>
    <Text>
      Interested in seeing what Pokemon there are?
      How about ones that aren't released in Pokemon GO yet?
      <br />Check this out!
    </Text>
  </Article>

  <Article date="26 Jan 2018">
    <Title>
      <a href="/charts/raidboss/raidboss.aggron.html">Aggron</a> Is Now A Raid Boss!
    </Title>
    <Text>
      With the release of 23 more Pokemon from the Hoenn Region, another was added as a Raid Boss.
      <br />Check out what you can get!
    </Text>
  </Article>
</News>
