<News>
  <Article date="05 July 2018">
    <Title>
      New <a href="/tools/shoppingboxes.html">Shopping Boxes</a>
    </Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        Sorry I didn't get to this earlier, but new Shopping Boxes have shown up in conjunction with te Safari Zone events.
      </p>
      <br />
      <p>
        <b>FYI</b>: I found a bug where a lot of Legacy info <span class="NOTE">(most notably Move Sets)</span> was not being included.
        <br />That is now fixed.
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="02 July 2018">
    <Title>
      Changes to <a href="/charts/fieldresearch/">Field Research</a> and Shiny Rosalia
    </Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        With the Water Event concluded, the Event's Field Research tasks have discontinued.
        But surprisingly, the 7 tasks they "temporarily" changed, have disappeared instead of reverting.
        <br /> The Field Research chart has been updated to reflect this.
      </p>
      <p class="NOTE">
        (<b>NOTE</b>: Since I haven't been able to find a reliable source for rewards that are Items, I have removed them from the chart for now.)
      </p>
      <p>
        Also, <a href="/charts/fieldresearch/encounter.snorlax.html">Snorlax</a> is the current Encounter complete a Research Breakthrough. <span class="NOTE" >(When you complete 7 days of Research tasks.)</span>
      </p>
      <br />
      <p>
        In other news, The shiny version of Rosalia has been released, and they have announced that Articuno will also be available as a shiny on 7 July.
        <br />The appropriate tables have been updated to show both.
        <br /><span class="NOTE">(And I'll put the Articuno on the Raid Boss chart even though it won't be available until Saturday.)</span>
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="26 June 2018">
    <Title>New Alola Forms</Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        The Alola form for several Pokemon has been released and there are more to come!
        <br />The various charts have been updated.
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="21 June 2018">
    <Title>Regice as Raid Boss!</Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        This morning it was announced that <a href="/charts/raidboss/raidboss.regice.html">Regice</a> will now be a Raid Boss!
        <br />I have updated the <a href="/charts/raidboss">Raid Bosses Chart</a>.
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
</News>
