<News>
  <Article date="16 October 2018">
    <Title>
      <a href="tech/GAME_MASTER/pokestats/pokestats.gen4.html">Gen 4</a> Is Here!!!
    </Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        Not sure which ones are released yet. I have activated the ones that seem to have reliable reports.
        <br /><span class="NOTE">(I'll update it as fast as I am able.)</span>
      </p>
      <p>
        Also, I have updated the <a href="tools/shoppingboxes.html">Shopping Boxes</a>
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="03 October 2018">
    <Title>
      Shiny Krabby and New Encounters for October
    </Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        Shiny Krabby has appeared and I have updated the appropriate charts.
      </p>
      <p>
        And, for the month of October, there have been changes to the Research Tasks.
        I have updated the <a href="charts/research/">Encounters Chart</a>.
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="28 September 2018">
    <Title>
      Deoxys Raids!
    </Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        The new GAME_MASTER with Deoxys stats was released on Wednesday.
        <br />However, the stats are a lot lower than I expected.
        Take a look at the possibilites on the <a href="charts/raidboss/">Raid Bosses</a> charts.
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="23 September 2018">
    <Title>
      New EX Raids
    </Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        MewTwo is now available as a plain Tier 5 Raid Boss <span class="EMPASIS">-And-</span> it has been announced that the new EX Raid Boss will be Deoxys!
        <br />As such, I have updated the Raid Boss charts.
        <br />
        <br /><span class="EMPHASIS">However</span>, the current GAME_MASTER file doesn't have the base stats for Deoxys,
        so I have no no way to create an accurate chart.
        As such, I have put Deoxyx as a placeholder in the Raid Boss Charts, but have left them disabled.
        <br /><span class="NOTE">(I'll keep an eye out for a new GAME_MASTER and will update as soon as the Deoxys stats are there.)</span>
      </p>
      <p>
        Oh yeah, for the Community Event yesterday, Chikorita (and its evolutions) can now be shiny.
        <br />And, if you evolved a Meganium during the event, it learned the Charged Move Frenzy Plant, which would now be considered a Legacy move.
        The appropriate charts have been updated.
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
</News>
