<News>
  <Article date="05 November 2018">
    <Title>
      More Shinies!
      <br /><span class="NOTE">(and Shopping Boxes)</span>
    </Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        Now you can get Ponytas and Cubones as Shiny!
        <br /><span class="NOTE">(I have updated the charts.)</span>
      </p>
      <p>
        Also, I'm not sure when it happened, but <a href="/tools/shoppingboxes.html">Shopping Boxes</a> changed, so I have updated them.
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="03 November 2018">
    <Title>
      A Bunch of Stuff!
    </Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        For November there is a new set of Research Tasks centered on Bug types.
        <span class="NOTE">(Catching 5 Bug-type Pokemon allows you to catch a <a href="charts/research/encounter/encounter.nincada.html">Nincada</a>!)</span>
        <br />And, for the 7<superscript>th</superscript> day Research Breakthrough you can catch a <a href="charts/research/encounter/encounter.shedinja.html">Shedinja</a>!
        <br />I have updated the <a href="charts/research/">Encounters Chart</a>.
      </p>
      <p>
        And, there are new shinies, including Pinsir and Caterpie.
      </p>
      <p>
        Gengars will be Raid Bosses during a special event on Saturday 03 November, and they may be shiny too!
        It is assumed they will be a Tier 4 boss, and I am assuming Gastlies and Haunters may be shiny too.
        <br />I have temporarily moved Genger from a Tier 3 to a Tier 4 <a href="charts/raidboss/raidboss.gengar.html">Raid Boss</a>, and marked them as shiny.
      </p>
      <p>
        <span class="EMPHISIS">UPDATE</span>: Gengar Raid Bosses have the Move Set Lick, Psychic, and I have updated the Move Set Chart.
        <span class="NOTE">(Psychic is pretty bad for a Gengar, but Lick is really good!)</span>
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>
  <Article date="23 October 2018">
    <Title>
      Halloween Event
    </Title>
    <Text>
      <p>
        Oh! There is so much!
      </p>
      <p>
        First of all, more Gen 4 Pokemon are being released.
        I will update the charts as I find out about them.
      </p>
      <p>
        Then, Mewtwo is no longer a Raid Boss, but the Gen 4 Pokemon <a href="charts/raidboss/raidboss.giratina.altered.html">Giratina</a> will be replacing it.
      </p>
      <p>
        And finally, there is a new Special Research Task <a href="charts/research/a_spooky_message.html">A Spooky Message</a>.
       <br /><span class="NOTE">(I will be updating it as I find out what each step is.)</span>
      </p>
    </Text>
  </Article>


</News>
